<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>

<!--=====================================================================================================================================================================
	Western Goods Trader Tasks
======================================================================================================================================================================-->

	<!--=================================================================================================================================================================
		ACT 1 - HELICOPTER DELIVERY
	==================================================================================================================================================================-->
	
	<!--=================================================================================================================================================================
		TASK 1 - ROAD BUMPS
	==================================================================================================================================================================-->

	<!-- Task strings -->
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_1_title">
		<text>Helicopter Delivery : Road Bumps</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_1_stage_0_descr">
		<text>Williams Heades was awaiting a resupply by helicopter, but the crew stop responding. Follow their GPS signal and see if everything is all right.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_1_stage_1_descr">
		<text>The helicopter is empty. The crew isn't here. Their GPS signal is active at a sawmill not far. Head over there.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_1_stage_2_descr">
		<text>Some of the supplies are missing, but there are a few of them left. Take them and return them.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_1_stage_3_descr">
		<text>The crew is dead. Bring back what remains of the shipment to Williams Heades.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_1_job_descr">
		<text>You want to help me? I'm awaiting a delivery. The shipment is being conveyed with a helicopter towards Zaton.\n \nProblem is, I've sent multiple messages to the crew of the helicopter, and they won't answer me. These guys are real pros, so I'm not too worried. I'd go out there and check myself, but I need to meet someone important here soon.\n \nCan you go to the delivery point, and see if everything is all right? Tell the crew I sent you. And tell them to answer the god-damn messages, while you're at it.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_1_task_complete_descr">
		<text>You made it! Thank god... This whole delivery is such a mess. So, the crew was dead? Damn it. These guys were tough, whatever got them must be serious business. At least you were able to recover some of it. I wonder where the rest went. Hell, I wonder why they even left the helicopter behind.\n \nI'll ask the guys at the Waste Processing Station in Zaton to go investigate. I cannot have that happen again. It's hard enough getting these supplies in the Zone, I don't need stuff like this to happen everytime.\n \nAnyway, thanks for your help Stalker. Good to know I can count on you.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- Messages strings -->
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_1_stage_0_message_1">
		<text>You made it to the helicopter?</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_1_stage_0_message_2">
		<text>Yes, but there's no-one here. The helicopter is landed in the middle of nowhere.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_1_stage_0_message_3">
		<text>Where's the crew?</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_1_stage_0_message_4">
		<text>I don't know. Do you have any way to locate them or the supplies?</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_1_stage_0_message_5">
		<text>Some of the supplies have a GPS tracker, let me check.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_1_stage_0_message_6">
		<text>I have a signal active at the sawmill, not far from you. Get over there, double time!</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_1_stage_1_message_1">
		<text>I've located the crew... They are all dead. It seems they tried to take cover in a house... And got overwhelmed by zombies.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_1_stage_1_message_2">
		<text>They are all dead? Damn it. Can you see any of the supplies?</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_1_stage_1_message_3">
		<text>I think I see a transport case.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_1_stage_1_message_4">
		<text>Only one? There should be a lot more! Doesn't matter. Take what you can and get the hell out of here before the zombies get you too!</text>
	</string>
	
	<!--=================================================================================================================================================================
		TASK 2 - CONSPIRACY
	==================================================================================================================================================================-->
	
	<!-- Task strings -->
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_2_title">
		<text>Helicopter Delivery : Conspiracy</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_2_stage_0_descr">
		<text>The Mercs at the Waste Processing Station secured the helicopter. Some of its electronics were fried. Some Stalkers over at Yanov station talk about strange lights. Continue the investigation from here.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_2_stage_1_descr">
		<text>The stalker you found at Yanov station talked about strange lights coming from the Container Warehouse. Keep investigating.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_2_stage_2_descr">
		<text>The helicopter has spotted bandit reinforcements ! Defend your position.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_2_stage_3_descr">
		<text>Find clues that could explain what happened to the helicopter.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_2_stage_4_descr">
		<text>Bring back the clues you found to Williams Heades.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_2_job_descr">
		<text>You remember the helicopter delivery you help me with? Well, I sent a few squads to secure and retrieve the helicopter. They spent hours getting its electronics back in shape. Half of it was fried. Anyway, thankfully they were able to get it flying again, helicopters aren't exactly cheap.\n \nI really don't like what's happening. I've heard rumors a group of bandits settled at the Container Warehouse in Jupiter. Some Stalkers over at Yanov station keep saying they see bright flashes at night coming from that place. The helicopter flew over that place, so I worried the two might be connected.\n \nCould you go there and clarify just what is going on?</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_2_task_complete_descr">
		<text>You made it back! Nice, did you find anything?\n \nLet's see... Hm, so it was just Bandits? You see, this is exactly what I told you. I don't care about conflicts in the Zone, I take people for what they are. Except for Bandits. I don't know why Dushman wants to keep good relations with them. We should just eradicate them all. Vermin.\n \nAnyway - sorry, I got carried away - Thank you for helping me to figure this whole thing out. At least it wasn't a targeted attack, so business shouldn't be impacted too much.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- Unique NPCs -->
	
	<string id="western_goods_jupiter_informant_name">
		<text>Sergei Karlovskiy</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="western_goods_jupiter_informant_bio">
		<text>No information.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- Dialogs strings -->
	
	<string id="western_goods_jupiter_informant_meet_0">
		<text>Hi. I'm looking for information.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="western_goods_jupiter_informant_meet_1">
		<text>Yeah? What kind exactly?</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="western_goods_jupiter_informant_meet_2">
		<text>I've heard some rumors are going around the place about "strange lights"? Do you know anything about that?</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="western_goods_jupiter_informant_meet_3">
		<text>Oh yeah, everyone here does. You know the Container Warehouse, south of here? I don't know what's going on there but a few nights ago it was a real firework.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="western_goods_jupiter_informant_meet_4">
		<text>Do you know what these lights could be? Perhaps an anomaly?</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="western_goods_jupiter_informant_meet_5">
		<text>I'm not sure. And to be honest, I'm not sure if I want to know either.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="western_goods_jupiter_informant_meet_6">
		<text>Alright. Thanks.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- Messages strings -->
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_2_stage_0_message_1">
		<text>I found someone at Yanov station. He said he saw strange lights coming from the Container Warehouse.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_2_stage_0_message_2">
		<text>Hm. The helicopter flew over that area when we lost contact with the crew.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_2_stage_0_message_3">
		<text>I'll make my way there, see what's going on.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_2_stage_0_message_4">
		<text>The helicopter, is operational again. I'll send it over to your location to assist you. We don't have a lot of fuel left, so make the best of it.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_2_stage_1_message_1">
		<text>We're in route to your location. Heades said you might need some covering fire. Just designate the targets, and we'll take care of the rest.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_2_stage_1_message_2">
		<text>We're running now on fuel. We'll return to the Waste Processing Station. Good luck out there.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_2_stage_1_message_3">
		<text>What are you doing, stealing our stuff. Dumb ass.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_2_stage_1_message_4">
		<text>Stealing our stuff? I'll tell the boys who you really are.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_2_stage_2_message_1">
		<text>Be advised, multiple Bandit squads moving in to your position.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_2_stage_2_message_2">
		<text>We're running now on fuel. We'll return to the Waste Processing Station. Good luck out there.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_2_heli_attack_1">
		<text>Target acquired.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_2_heli_attack_2">
		<text>Roger that.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_2_heli_attack_3">
		<text>Solid copy.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_2_heli_attack_4">
		<text>Opening fire.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_2_heli_attack_5">
		<text>Stand clear.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!--=================================================================================================================================================================
		TASK 3 - THE RESCUE
	==================================================================================================================================================================-->
	
	<!-- Task strings -->
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_3_title">
		<text>Helicopter Delivery : The Rescue</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_3_stage_0_descr">
		<text>A mercenary scouting team spotted what seems to be one of their own, captured by Monolith forces. Rescue him.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_3_stage_1_descr">
		<text>The rescued Merc isn't in good shape. Escort him safely to the bridge, in the Red Forest, where he will be evacuated.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_3_stage_2_descr">
		<text>Enemies across the bridge will prevent the helicopter from landing. Clear the area.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_3_stage_3_descr">
		<text>Wait for the helicopter to pick up the rescued Merc.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_3_stage_4_descr">
		<text>The Merc was successfully rescued and extracted. Come back to Williams Heades.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_3_job_descr">
		<text>I'm glad you ask. There is a situation you can help me with. We often send squads deep into the Zone to keep track of enemy movements, and define safe corridors for the helicopters to go through.\n \nA few hours ago, one of our squads came back and said the spotted a stalker taken hostage by a Monolith group. They said it could have been one of our own, but they couldn't get close enough to make sure. And considering how many Monolithians they spotted, no-one wants to go there and find out.\n \nI know it's a tall ask, but could you head there and make sure we're not leaving someone behind?</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_3_task_complete_descr">
		<text>I knew you were the right person for the job! Thanks for rescuing him.\n \nI don't know if he was able to tell you when you escorted him back to the Red Forest, but he was actually the co-pilot from the first crew of the helicopter, the one you found dead in the Sawmill at Zaton.\n \nAnyway the helicopter dropped him off here about an hour ago, I gave him some meds to try and tame his confusion.\n \nOh, before I forget, he said he wanted to see you.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- Unique NPCs -->
	
	<string id="western_goods_crew_member_name">
		<text>Patrick "Odysseus" Dunbar</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="western_goods_crew_member_bio">
		<text>One of the members of the helicopter.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="stalker_crew_member_start_0">
		<text>How come you are even talking to me yet?! We're supposed to meet in act 1, task 3. I'll send you to Brazil be careful !</text>
	</string>

	<string id="stalker_crew_member_start_1">
		<text>Uhh... Wh-wh...</text>
	</string>

	<string id="stalker_crew_member_start_2">
		<text>Wha-what's... going on?</text>
	</string>

	<string id="stalker_crew_member_start_3">
		<text>Where are you... taking me?</text>
	</string>

	<string id="stalker_crew_member_start_4">
		<text>We should get moving, I don't like staying here...</text>
	</string>

	<string id="stalker_crew_member_start_5">
		<text>Good to see you again.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="stalker_crew_member_start_6">
		<text>Hey friend, I'm happy to see you!</text>
	</string>
		
	<!-- Dialogs strings -->

	<string id="stalker_crew_member_rescue_0">
		<text>Hey, you're still with us? Get hold of yourself, and come with me, fast!</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="stalker_crew_member_rescue_1">
		<text>Hmm. Wh-who are you?</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="stalker_crew_member_rescue_2">
		<text>A scout team spotted you some time ago, I'm getting you out of here.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="stalker_crew_member_rescue_3">
		<text>My head...</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="stalker_crew_member_rescue_4">
		<text>Come on! We don't have a lot of time before the Monolith squads nearby will call for reinforcements. Come!</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="stalker_crew_member_reward_0"> 
		<text>Hey, Heades said you wanted to see me?</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="stalker_crew_member_reward_1">
		<text>Yes. I wanted to personally thank you for coming to my rescue. You know, these days it's hard to find people that don't take the opportunity to screw over others when they can.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="stalker_crew_member_reward_2">
		<text>I'm just not that kind of person. I'm glad I made it in time before the Monolith could brainwash you.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="stalker_crew_member_reward_3">
		<text>Yeah, tell me about it! Anyway, I wanted to give you a little something, to make my thank just a little more than a word.\n \nHere, take this. It's an artefact my friends and I found when we last went hunting. I can't believe they are all dead... An artefact isn't exactly the same as saving a life, but I heard it's quite valuable.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="stalker_crew_member_reward_4">
		<text>Thank you.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- Messages strings -->
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_3_stage_0_message_1">
		<text>Heades, I found the captured merc. He's shaken, but alive.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_3_stage_0_message_2">
		<text>Good. Can you escort him back to the Book Store?</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_3_stage_0_message_3">
		<text>He is really confused, I doubt he'll even be able to fire a gun. The Book Store isn't exactly close to our position...</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_3_stage_0_message_4">
		<text>Can you get to the bridge, in the Red Forest? I'll arrange the helicopter to go pick him up.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_3_stage_0_message_5">
		<text>That would work. Have the helicopter stand by, I'll tell you when to send them to our location.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_3_stage_1_message_1">
		<text>H-how... How d-did you find me again?</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_3_stage_1_message_2">
		<text>Heades told me a scout team found you when they were looking for enemy movements and safe air corridors for his helicopters.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_3_stage_1_message_3">
		<text>Are you feeling better?</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_3_stage_1_message_4">
		<text>Yeah I'm... I'm alright. My memory is a bit fuzzy...</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_3_stage_1_message_5">
		<text>You remember who you are at least? I hope these Monolithians didn't have time to start working on you.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_3_stage_1_message_6">
		<text>Yeah no don't worry. I remember. I'm copilot for one of Heades' helicopters.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_3_stage_1_message_7">
		<text>Wait, you said you're a copilot? How come Heades didn't notice you were missing?</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_3_stage_1_message_8">
		<text>I don't know... All I remember is, we were flying some cargo to the Water Processing Station in Zaton, and we had to land in emergency...</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_3_stage_1_message_9">
		<text>You're the copilot of the helicopter I found abandoned in Zaton?! You just forgot to mention that?</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_3_stage_1_message_10">
		<text>Sorry I'm still a bit confused. Anyway, I'm probably still alive because those Monolithians wanted me to fly one of their own helicopters.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_3_stage_3_message_1">
		<text>The area is safe enough. You can send the helicopter over.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wg_trader_act_1_task_3_stage_3_message_2">
		<text>Roger that, we're on our way. Hang tight.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!--=================================================================================================================================================================
		ACT 2 - SMUGGLERS 
	==================================================================================================================================================================-->

	<!--=================================================================================================================================================================
		TASK 1 - GATHER INFORMATION 
	==================================================================================================================================================================-->
	
	<!--=================================================================================================================================================================
		TASK 2 - CONFRONT THE SMUGGLER
	==================================================================================================================================================================-->
	
<!--=====================================================================================================================================================================
	Western Goods Trader Quest Items
======================================================================================================================================================================-->

	<!-- Supply case -->
	
	<string id="st_wg_act_1_task_1_quest_item">
		<text>Supply case</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_act_1_task_1_quest_item_s">
		<text>Supplies</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_act_1_task_1_quest_item_descr">
		<text>
			A sealed case found near the corpses of the helicopter crew. The exact contents of the case are unknown, but since it was to be delivered to Williams Heades, it must contain western goods.\n
			\n
			%c[ui_gray_1]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] imported\n
			%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] highly valuable\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- Unidentified weapon -->
	
	<string id="st_wg_act_1_task_2_quest_item_1">
		<text>Unidentified weapon</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_act_1_task_2_quest_item_1_s">
		<text>Unidentified weapon</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_act_1_task_2_quest_item_1_descr">
		<text>
			An unknown weapon, the firing mechanism of which has not been established. The weapon appears to be out of ammunition - squeezing the trigger doesn't do anything. It's very heavy and definitely high-tech. Of note is that it appears not to fire bullets based on ignition. Most probably, the rounds are propelled by electro-magnetic forces. One can only suspect what kind of destructive potential it possesses.\n
			\n
			%c[ui_gray_1]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_red] • %c[ui_gray_2] unusable\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- Bandit's note -->
	
	<string id="st_wg_act_1_task_2_quest_item_2">
		<text>Bandit's note</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_act_1_task_2_quest_item_2_s">
		<text>Bandit's note</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wg_act_1_task_2_quest_item_2_descr">
		<text>
			A paper note found at the container warehouse. Judging by the writing, it was definitely written by one of the bandits...
		</text>
	</string>

</string_table>