<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<!--=================================================================================================================-->
<!--                                                                                                                 -->
<!--    Original Author(s) : NLTP_ASHES                                                                              -->
<!--    Edited : N/A                                                                                                 -->
<!--    Date : 12/12/2023                                                                                            -->
<!--    License : Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International (CC BY-NC-SA 4.0)          -->
<!--                                                                                                                 -->
<!--    Translation file for Western Goods' entries in the PDA Guide.                                                -->
<!--                                                                                                                 -->
<!--=================================================================================================================-->
<string_table>

    <!-- Western goods trader encyclopedia entry -->
    <string id="encyclopedia_characters_western_goods_ashes">
        <text>Williams "Ashes" Heades</text>
    </string>

    <string id="encyclopedia_characters_western_goods_ashes_text">
        <text>
        %c[pda_white]Williams "Ashes" Heades%c[ui_gray_1] is a trader. He hangs around at the Book Store (Pripyat Outskirts).\n
        \n%c[pda_green]Information%c[ui_gray_1]\n
        \nWilliams "Ashes" Heades is a member of the Mercenaries. Former UN soldier, he was sent to multiple theaters of war as part of UN task forces. He fought the civil war in the 2010 rebellion in Altis, Greece.\n
        \nHe was later sent to the Chornobyl exclusion zone as part of a special UNISG deployment. Not a lot is known about what he was tasked with, all that people know is he decided to stay and did not leave with the rest of the deployment.\n
        \n%c[pda_yellow]Trivia%c[ui_gray_1]\n
        \n• This trader is the main importer for western goods in the Zone.
        </text>
    </string>

    <!-- GPS locator encyclopedia entry -->
    <string id="encyclopedia_items_western_goods_gps">
        <text>GPS Locator</text>
    </string>

    <string id="encyclopedia_items_western_goods_gps_text">
        <text>
        The %c[pda_white]GPS locator%c[ui_gray_1] is a device used to identify the distance and name to the closest area.\n
        \n%c[pda_green]Information%c[ui_gray_1]\n
        \nA military grade GPS device used to identify, and find the distance to the closest area near the user. It also displays the global region the user is located in.\n
        \nA special technology is used for the screen of the device, allowing it to display information with very minimal power use. The downside of that is that the screen cannot display colors.\n
        \n• %c[pda_white]Extremely low power consumption%c[ui_gray_1]. Needs recharging about once a year depending on use.
        </text>
    </string>

    <!-- BIC Lighter encyclopedia entry -->
    <!-- TODO: Add RUS translation -->
    <string id="encyclopedia_items_western_goods_bic_lighter">
        <text>BIC Lighter</text>
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Add RUS translation -->
    <string id="encyclopedia_items_western_goods_bic_lighter_text">
        <text>
            The %c[pda_white]BIC lighter%c[ui_gray_1] is a small and disposable lighter that can be used to light up your surroundings, but also to ignite a number of things.\n
            \n%c[pda_green]Information%c[ui_gray_1]\n
            \nThe BIC lighter is a powerful tool in the Zone. Many Stalkers use it to light up cigarettes. But it is strong enough to light up campfires (equip and pull the lighter out to do so). It also provides a small light, which can be used to light up your immediate surroundings while remaining somewhat discrete, especially at night.
        </text>
    </string>

    <!-- SigSauer KILO5K encyclopedia entry -->
    <!-- TODO: Add RUS translation -->
    <string id="encyclopedia_items_western_goods_rangefinder">
        <text>SigSauer KILO5K</text>
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Add RUS translation -->
    <string id="encyclopedia_items_western_goods_rangefinder_text">
        <text>
            The %c[pda_white]SigSauer KILO5K%c[ui_gray_1] is a laser rangefinder that can be used to read distances to a target.\n
            \n%c[pda_green]Information%c[ui_gray_1]\n
            \nThis compact and robust rangefinder is a powerful tool to measure distances to various targets. It measures the Line of Sight (LOS) distance, that is, a direct line from the rangefinder to the target. It also measures the Horizontal Component Distance (HCD), a two-dimensional distance (not taking in elevation) from the rangefinder to the target.\n
            \nTo ensure a consistent comfort of use, the rangefinder has two color modes, red (optimal during day) and green (optimal during night under night vision goggles).
        </text>
    </string>

    <!-- Flea Market encyclopedia entry -->
    <string id="encyclopedia_features_western_goods_flea">
        <text>Flea Market</text>
    </string>

    <string id="encyclopedia_features_western_goods_flea_text">
        <text>
            The %c[pda_white]Flea Market%c[ui_gray_1] allows the player to purchase temporary offers, where items come in multiple units, but at a discount.\n
            \n%c[pda_green]Information%c[ui_gray_1]\n
            \nBy talking to a trader at the Flea Market, the player has the option to purchase special offers. These offers are limited in time, and will eventually expire and get replaced with newer offers.\n
            \nOffers consist of the following:\n
            \n• %c[pda_white]Item%c[ui_gray_1]. The item contained in the offer;
            \n• %c[pda_white]Quantity%c[ui_gray_1]. The quantity of the item contained in the offer. Randomized between 2 and 10 items;
            \n• %c[pda_white]Discount%c[ui_gray_1]. The discount applied compared to the regular price. Randomized between 5% and 50%;
            \n• %c[pda_white]Price%c[ui_gray_1]. The money required to accept the offer.
        </text>
    </string>

    <!-- Oleksandr Chernenko encyclopedia entry -->
    <string id="encyclopedia_characters_western_goods_oleksandr">
        <text>Captain Oleksandr Chernenko</text>
    </string>

    <string id="encyclopedia_characters_western_goods_oleksandr_text">
        <text>
            %c[pda_white]Captain Oleksandr Chernenko%c[ui_gray_1] is a trader. He can be found at the Flea Market (Garbage).\n
            \n%c[pda_green]Information%c[ui_gray_1]\n
            \nCaptain Oleksandr Chernenko is a former Army soldier, turned Mercenary. He said he deserted when the army tasked him with a suicide mission, although little details are know about what this mission was, as he seems to not enjoy talking about it.\n
            \nThese days, he can be found in the basement of the Flea Market, at the Garbage. He offers packages of items, at a discount. The sale of these packages is usually limited in time.\n
            \n%c[pda_yellow]Trivia%c[ui_gray_1]\n
            \n• This trader manages the Mercenary's flea market offerings;
            \n• This trader can sometimes sell packages containing western goods.
        </text>
    </string>

    <!-- Hand drawn map encyclopedia entry -->
    <string id="encyclopedia__notes_western_goods_hand_drawn_map">
        <text>Hand drawn map</text>
    </string>

    <string id="encyclopedia__notes_western_goods_hand_drawn_map_text">
        <text>\n</text>
    </string>

</string_table>